- 준비 됐어요
- 정말이야?
-I'm ready.
-You sure?
헬멧부터 똑바로
쓰고 하자
Let me just straighten out
your helmet there.
- 고마워요, 아빠
- 아빤 하나고 엄마가 둘이지
-Thanks, Daddy.
-No, no. One daddy, two mommies.
- 좋아, 이제 타 봐
- 좋아
-All right, it's all yours.
-Okay, okay.
아주 잘 하네
There you go, there you go.
와, 벤이 처음으로
큰 자전거를 타다니!
Wow, Ben's first big kid's bike.
This is so exciting!
내 자전거 생각난다
Oh, yeah, I remember mine.
6살 생일때 였는데
공원에 가서
It was my sixth birthday.
I went to the park...
- 올라탔더니 휘어버렸지
- 맞아
-and I got on it and it bent.
-Yeah.
- 난 자전거 못 가져봤는데
- 뭐?
-I never had a bike of my own.
-What?
집이 가난했거든
We didn't have a lot of money.
길 건너집 애는 끝내주는
자전거가 있었지
But the girl across the street
had the best bike.
분홍색에 무지개색 술과
종이 달려 있었고
It was pink and it had rainbow-colored
tassels hanging off the handles...
플라스틱 꽃으로 장식된
and a bell
and this big, white wicker basket...
크고 하얀 바구니가
달려 있었지
with those
plastic daisies stuck on.
내 처음 자전거와 똑같네
That sounds like my first bike.
난 아버지 걸 물려받았어
My dad gave me his old one.
- 너도 태워줬니?
- 아니
-Did the girl ever let you ride it?
-No.
자전거 포장 박스는
주던 걸
But she gave me the box
that it came in.
앞에 자전거 그림이 있었지
It had a picture of the bike
on the front.
거기 앉으면 양아빠가
마당에서 끌어주셨어
So I would sit on it and my stepdad
would drag me around the backyard.
너무 불공평해
That is so unfair.
아냐, 나도 끌어 드렸는 걸
Not really, I got
to drag him around too.
The One With All the Candy
Hey, what are you guys doing?
얘들아, 뭐하니?
Making candy for the neighbors.
이웃들 줄 사탕 만들고 있어
I'm sorry, who?
누굴 준다고?
I'm gonna hang
a basket on the door.
문에 사탕 바구니를
달아 둘 거야
When the neighbors walk by,
they can take a piece.
지나가다 누구든
꺼내갈 수 있게 말야
-But we don't know the neighbors.
-I do.
- 아는 사람도 없잖아
- 난 있어
There's, let's see,
the guy with the mustache...
어디 보자
수염 달린 아저씨
smokes-a-lot lady,
some kids I've seen...
골초 아줌마, 애들 몇 명
and the red-haired guy
who does not like to be called Rusty.
러스티라고 부르면
싫어하는 빨간머리 아저씨
그러니까 내가
사탕을 만드는 거야
See, this is exactly why
I'm making this candy.
그래야 이웃을 알지
We can get to know our neighbors.
Wouldn't it be easier
if we just moved?
차라리 이사가는 게
쉽지 않을까?
좋은 아침!
Good morning!
- 기분이 좋아 보이네
- 안 좋을 이유가 없잖아?
-Somebody's in a good mood.
-Well, why shouldn't I be?
좋은 친구들에
끝내주는 직장에
I have great friends.
I have a wonderful job..
비서랑 놀아날 수
있으니까
Where you can make out
with your assistant.
별 일도 아냐
It's not a big deal.
우리 사이가 일에 문제 안 되게
밤새 계획을 짰어
We stayed up creating a plan so
that us dating won't be a problem.
그래? 무슨 계획?
Oh, yeah? What's the plan?
그냥...
We.. We are not...
문제가 되지 않게
going to let it...
한다는 거지
be a problem.
그 계획 세우느라
밤을 샜다고?
It took you all night
to come up with that plan?
그리고 다른 일도 좀 했지
Well, you know,
we did other stuff too.
Did you two...?
그럼 너희 둘...
Oh, I don't sleep with guys
on the first date.
난 첫 데이트부터
자지는 않아
- 매트, 마크, 벤...
- 더 이상은!
-Matt Wire, Mark Lynn, Ben Wise..
-Anymore!
태그, 나 오늘 회의
있는 거 맞죠?
Hi, Tag, I have a conference call
today, is that correct?
- 네, 4시에요
- 좋아요, 됐어요
-Yes, at 4.
-Okay, thank you, that'll be all.
잠깐만
Wait, wait.
저거 봤어요?
우리 둘 사이에
Did you see that?
He had no idea there was
something going on between us.
무슨 일이 있는지
꿈에도 몰라요
- 나가봐야 겠네요
- 그래요, 일벌레씨
-I'd better get back to my desk.
-Okay, hard worker.
평가서에 적어줄게요
I'll put that in your evaluation.
- 평가서요?
- 일한 지 두 달 됐잖아요
-My what?
-You've been here for two months now.
직장 상사가 평가서를
쓰게 되어 있거든요
And your boss is required to hand in
a performance evaluation.
그런데 한 가지
평가할 게 남았어요
But you know, there is one thing
that I have yet to evaluate.
- 진심이에요?
- 아뇨, 한 번 해보고 싶었거든요
-Are you serious?
-No, but I've always wanted to do that.
치우는 거 도와줄래요?
Can you help me clean this up?
The basket is totally empty!
The neighbors ate it all!
바구니가 텅 비었어!
이웃들이 다 가져갔어!
Well, either that or...
그렇거나 아니면...
Joey!
조이!
Yeah?
왜?
-Did you eat all the neighbor candy?
-That was the plan.
- 사탕 네가 다 먹었어?
- 그러려고 했는데
When I got to it,
there was only a few pieces left.
가보니 몇 개
안 남았던 걸
They've come by all day.
They love it.
계속 오던 걸
아주 맛있나 봐
They love my candy?
내 사탕을 좋아해?
-Oh, man, I gotta go make more.
-Hey, Mon.
- 야, 더 만들어야겠다
- 모니카
Make some more lasagna too. Something
might have happened to a chunk of it.
이왕이면 라자냐도 만들어
좀 없어졌을 거야
로스, 이웃들이
사탕 다 가져갔어
Ross, the neighbors ate all my candy.
Mine stole my newspaper.
내 이웃은 신문 훔쳐갔어
It's like a crime wave.
범죄 소굴도 아니고
Phoebe, you got a second?
피비, 시간 있어?
Sure.
그래
자전거 얘기 들은 후론
Ever since you told me
about that bike...
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
계속 그 생각이 나서
어렸을 때 누구나
자전거가 있잖아, 그래서...
I mean, everyone should have
a first bike, you know? So...
어머나, 로스!
Oh, my God, Ross!
- 마음에 들어?
- 너무 좋아!
-You like it?
-I love it!
- 그래?
- 어머나
-Yeah?
-Oh, oh, God..
사랑해
And I love you.
그런 뜻으론 말고
Not that way.
But the bike got you a lot closer.
자전거 때문에 더 좋아졌어
Well, take it downstairs.
내려가자
You know, give it a test drive.
시운전 해 봐야지
Okay. Oh, my God.
좋아, 맙소사
My first bike!
자전거를 갖게 됐어!
Thank you for the best present
I've ever gotten.
생애 최고의 선물을
줘서 고마워
You're welcome.
별 소릴
Oh, and Chandler's about to cry.
챈들러 울려고 한다
Am not.
아냐
Who is that?
누구지?
Don't worry, I'm brave.
걱정 마, 난 겁 안나
I.. I am brave.
겁 하나도 안 나
No, no, no, no!
안 돼, 안 돼!
Can you tell me who is there, please?
밖에 누구시죠?
My name's Gary. I live upstairs.
전 개리예요
위층에 살죠
-Hi.
- 안녕하세요
-Do you know what time it is?
-It's candy time.
- 지금 몇 신 줄 아세요?
- 사탕 먹을 시간이요
제 룸메이트가 사탕이
천국의 맛이라던데요
My roommate says they taste
like little drops of heaven.
과찬의 말씀을
Oh, please.
들었어?
'천국의 맛'이래
Did you hear that?
"Little drops of heaven."
새벽 4시야
Four a.m.
사탕 좀 주실래요?
So can I get some candy?
I am sorry, but some of us
have to get up early and go to work.
미안하지만 일찍 일어나
출근해야 하는 사람도 있어요
He does not know
that I am not "some of us."
저 사람은 내가 거기
포함 안 되는 거 몰라
죄송한데
아침에 넣어 놓을게요
I'm sorry, but I'll put some out
in the morning.
좋아요, 다시 오죠
Okay, I'll swing by later.
여기 사셨어요?
You live in this building?
봤음 기억했을 텐데
Seems like I'd remember you.
잘 가요, 개리
Night, Gar.
So did you read your evaluation yet?
평가서 읽어봤어요?
'극비'라고 써 있어서
안 읽고
No, it was marked "confidential."
바로 인사과로 보냈죠
I just sent it to human resources.
농담하는 거죠?
장난으로 썼는데
Please, you're kidding, right?
I wrote that one as a joke for you.
A joke they would appreciate?
인사과가
좋아할 만한 장난?
I'm thinking, no.
아마 아닐 걸요
- 뭐라고 썼어요?
- 태그는 키스도 잘 하고
-What did you say?
-I said you were a good kisser...
작고 귀여운 엉덩이가
이쁘다고 했어요
and that I liked your
teeny, tiny tushy.
내 엉덩이요?
No, not my tushy.
더 있어요
It gets worse.
독창성 난에는
About your initiative, I wrote:
'별 무리없이 브래지어를
벗길 수 있다'고 썼고
"He was able to unhook my bra
with minimal supervision."
업무 상 문제에는
'문제없길 바람'이라고 했고
Under problems with performance,
I wrote, "Dear God, I hope not."
그리고, 스마일
얼굴도 그려 넣었죠
And then.. And then I drew
a little smiley face.
참, 야한 그림도 그렸고요
And then a small pornographic sketch.
피비한테 자전거
사 준 거 정말 잘했어
That is so sweet of you
to get Phoebe that bike.
그 얘기 듣고
울 뻔 했다니까
When I heard the story,
I almost cried.
울 뻔 해?
Almost cried, huh?
챈들러, 들었어?
울 '뻔' 했대
Hear that, Chandler? "Almost" cried.
넌 누가 타이타닉
얘기만 꺼내도 울잖아
Hey, you cry every time
somebody talks about Titanic.
그 둘은 서로밖에 없었어
Those two had only each other.
She really likes it, huh?
피비가 좋아한다
Oh, yeah. I saw her
walking it down the street.
그럼, 자전거 끌고
가는 거 봤어
바구니에 꽃도 넣었는데
너무 예쁘더라
She had these flowers in the basket.
It was so cute.
아침에도 봤는데
공원에서 끌고 가던걸
I saw her this morning,
walking it by the park.
잠깐, 자전걸 끌고 가?
Wait, she was walking the bike?
Both times?
두 번 다?
- 피비
- 안녕!
-Hey, Phoebe.
-Oh, hi!
- 자전거 좋아?
- 그럼, 너무 좋아
-Hey, so you enjoying the bike?
-Oh, uh-huh, so much.
피비, 너 자전거
탈 줄 아는 거지?
Phoebe, you do know how
to ride a bike, don't you?
그럼
Of course.
그럼 한 번 타 볼래?
Can we see you ride it?
Okay.
좋아
See?
봤어?
I told you not to get
involved with your assistant.
비서하곤 엮이지
말라고 했잖아
There's no such thing as a secret
when it comes to affairs.
사귀는 일을 비밀로
할 수는 없어
들었어, 챈들러?
Did you hear that, Chandler?
그런 일은 없다고
No such thing.
사탕먹는 사람한테
왜 그래?
What happened? I'm just eating candy.
내가 적은 걸 그대로
안 받아들일 지도 몰라
Maybe it's not that bad. They might
not take it the way I meant it.
그럼, '엉덩이'는
엉덩이 말고도
Absolutely, you know?
Because "tushy" can mean both ass...
좋은 일군이란 뜻도 되니까
and good worker.
다시 찾아와야 돼
I just gotta get the thing back.
레이첼? 네가 그렸단 그림
Rach? That sketch you mentioned?
이거와 비슷하지 않니?
Might it have looked
a little like this?
맙소사, 조이!
Oh, my God, Joey!
- 넌 왜 그 모양이냐?
- 기가 막혀!
-What is the matter with you?
-God!
포르노 살 돈 없을 때
유용하게 써 먹었다고
This little talent came in handy
before I could afford porn.
너무 늦은 거 아는데
사탕이 필요해서요
Hi, I'm sorry. I know it's
after hours, but I really need candy.
미안하지만 안 되겠어요
규칙은 규칙이니까요
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
See? Rules are rules.
제발요, 친구들이
먼데서 오는데
Please, I have people coming
from out of town today.
- 사탕 얘길 했거든요
- 정말요?
-I told them all about your candy.
-You're kidding.
먼데서 온다고요?
뭐라고 하셨어요?
Out-of-towners, huh?
What did you tell them?
말로 표현 못 할
정도라고요
I told them your candy
was absolutely indescribable.
Some people have said it's "little
drops of heaven." But whatever.
혹자는 '천국의 맛'이라고도
하더군요
-Please, can't you help me out?
-Hey, Chandler, do we know that lady?
- 좀 도와줘요
- 챈들러, 저 여자 알아?
Isn't she the woman who lives
below you and has sex really loud?
잠자리할 때 괴성 지르는
아래층 아줌마 아냐?
All right, I'll do it just this once.
좋아요, 이번 한 번뿐이에요
-But you can't tell anyone.
-Please, just give it to me.
- 그리고 절대 비밀이에요
- 그래요, 어서 줘요
Yeah, that's her.
그 아줌마 맞네
-Thank you.
-Unbelievable!
- 고마워요
- 말도 안 돼!
I can't believe that sign didn't work.
안내문도 소용없잖아
You know what would work?
Stop making candy.
사탕을 그만 만들면 되잖아
But they like it.
사람들이 사탕을 좋아하잖아
You mean they like you.
널 좋아한다는 거겠지
Maybe.
그럴 수도 있고
Is that why you became a chef,
so people would like you?
사람들 인기 얻으려고
요리사가 됐어?
You want to talk about getting
people to like you, huh, funny man?
네가 그런 얘기 할
자격 있어, 농담맨?
Just remember everything
I taught you and you'll be fine.
내가 가르친 대로만 하면
괜찮을 거야
Okay? Here we go.
알았지? 출발해
Ready, set..
준비
Wait, this seat
is really uncomfortable.
잠깐만, 이 의자
되게 불편하네
Maybe before we start
we should just get another one.
타기 전에 다른 의자로
바꾸는 게 좋겠어
비행기 좌석이나
콩자루 같은 걸로
Perhaps like an airplane seat,
or a beanbag chair!
너 절대 못 내려
자전거 배워야지
You can't get out of this.
You have to learn how to ride a bike.
왜? 왜 배워야 돼?
Why? Why do I have to learn?
- 응급 상황에 대비해서
- 무슨 응급 상황?
-Well, in case of an emergency.
-What kind of emergency?
어떤 남자가 총을
네 머리에 대고
Well, what if a man comes along
and puts a gun to your head and says:
'자전거 안 타면'
"You ride this bike or I'll..
'쏠 거요'하면 어쩔래?
I'll shoot you."
종을 울려
주의를 흩트린 다음
I would ring the bell to distract him.
중국 표창으로
총을 쳐내 버리지
Then I would knock the gun away
with a Chinese throwing star.
좋아, 피비, 자전거에 타
Okay, Phoebe, just get on the bike...
and, hey, I'll hold you up
and push you. Okay?
내가 잡고 밀어줄게
You won't let go?
안 놓을 거지?
-No.
-You swear?
- 그럼
- 맹세해?
I swear.
맹세해
-Okay.
-Come on.
- 좋아
- 어서
좋아, 간다, 됐지?
Here we go. All right?
All right?
- 됐어
- 됐지?
Feel good?
All right, try pedaling.
기분 좋지?
좋아, 페달을 밟아 봐
That's it, you're doing great.
Yes, take control.
잘 했어, 잘 하네
균형을 잡아 봐
Yes, yes, yes!
좋았어, 좋았어!
Oh, no!
안 돼!
You swore!
맹세해놓고!
-I just thought you were doing so well.
-I am shocked. Shocked!
- 너무 잘 타길래
- 충격이야!
원래 그렇게 배우는 거야
It's a legitimate learning technique.
Wow.
와
밖에서 사람들이
사탕 달라고 하는데
Hey, there's some people outside
asking about candy.
They'll just have to wait, okay?
I only got two hands!
기다려야지, 안 그래?
내 손은 두 개뿐인데
-Need some help?
-No, you don't know the system.
- 좀 도와줘?
- 안 돼, 시스템도 모르잖아
I don't need nobody messing
with the system!
시스템을 망치면 안 된다고
By the way, the week before your
wedding, you may not see a lot of me.
그나저나, 네 결혼식 전 주엔
나 많이 바쁠 거야
Oh, hello, liar.
안녕, 거짓말쟁이
Look, I'm really sorry
I let go of the bike.
자전거 놓은 거
정말 미안해
I could've been killed, you know.
죽을 수도 있었어
I know, I know.
그래 알아
다시 해 보면 안 될까?
But can we please try it again?
I mean, you were so close, Phoebe.
거의 성공했잖아
Well, I would love to...
나도 그러고 싶지만
but the bike got stolen
and the police have no suspects.
자전거를 도둑맞았고
용의자도 몰라
-Phoebe.
-What?
- 피비
- 왜?
What the hell?
이럴 수가?
You know what?
이렇게 하자
If you won't learn how to ride,
then I'm sorry...
자전거 타기 안 배우려면
-I have to take it back.
-But why?
- 자전거 돌려줘
- 뭐? 왜?
왜냐하면...
Because it's...
It'd be like you having this guitar...
네가 이 기타를 갖고
and never playing it.
안 치는 것과 같은 이치지
Okay, this guitar wants to be played.
이 기타는 연주를
해주길 바라고
And this bike wants to be ridden.
이 자전거는 누가
타주길 바란다구
And if you don't ride it...
그런데 안 타주면
you're killing its spirit.
영혼을 죽이는 거야
자전거가
The bike...
is dying.
죽어간다고
All right. If you care enough
to make up that load of crap, okay.
좋아, 그런 엉터리 얘기까지
지어내니 배울게
Great.
좋아, 잘 됐네
You're making the bike very happy.
자전거가 아주
기뻐할 거야
Okay, Ross.
알았다니까
Please don't die!
제발 죽지 마!
To get the evaluation
before they see it...
누가 읽기 전에
평가서를 가져오려면
we gotta get into Zelner's office.
He doesn't get in until 10.
젤너 부장 사무실에 들어가야 돼
부장님은 10시에 출근하는데
But his assistant, Betty, comes in
early to eat breakfast at her desk.
비서, 베티는 일찍 와서
자리에서 아침을 먹어요
-That's kind of sad.
-Yeah, well, Betty's kind of sad.
- 좀 처량하네요
- 베티가 원래 처량해요
Which is why I believe I can lure
her away with these chocolates.
그래서 이 초콜렛으로
유혹하려는 거죠
While I distract her, you go in.
그 때 태그가 들어가요
-Got it.
-Let's roll.
- 알았어요
- 시작하죠
Hello, Rachel. You got a minute?
레이첼, 시간 있어요?
Yeah, sure, Mr. Zelner.
For you? Anything. Minute.
네, 젤너 부장님께라면
시간을 내야죠
Okay, great.
좋아요, 잘 됐네요
Abort the plan.
계획 취소
Actually, I'd like to speak
to both of you.
사실 둘 다에게
할 얘기가 있어요
Okay.
네
Well, can we get you anything,
Mr. Zelner? Maybe some chocolates.
뭐 필요한 거라도?
초콜렛이라도?
No, thanks,
but I'll give these to Betty.
난 됐지만
베티 갖다 줄게요
So, I read your evaluation of Tag.
태그 평가서를 읽었어요
Or, to use his full name,
Tag "Sweet Cheeks" Jones?
태그 이름이 '귀염둥이'
태그 존스던가요?
Is something going on with you two?
두 사람 사귑니까?
Oh, my God,
can you imagine if there was?
맙소사
그렇게 생각하셨어요?
I mean, what would happen exactly?
그렇다면 어떻게 되죠?
Well, I'd be forced to file a report.
보고서를 올릴 수 밖에요
I'd have to consult
with the legal department.
법률 자문도
들어봐야 하고요
And your future at the company
would be in jeopardy.
그리고 회사에서
레이첼 장래도 불투명하죠
-Well..
-Mr. Zelner...
- 그렇다면...
- 부장님
I filled in that evaluation.
그 보고서 제가 썼습니다
-Oh, no..
-Yeah, yeah.
- 아니에요
- 맞습니다
I thought it would be funny.
재미있을 것 같아서요
You wrote that you have a cute tushy?
자기 엉덩이를 귀엽다고
썼단 말인가?
Yes.
네, 제가 좀 엉뚱해서요
I have a weird sense of humor.
And I'm kind of strangely
proud of my butt.
그리고 제 엉덩이에
자부심이 강하거든요
It's kind of a risky joke, Tag.
좀 위험한 농담일세, 태그
What is this drawing?
I can't figure it out.
이 그림은 뭔가?
난 봐도 모르겠는걸
It's upside down, you gotta..
It doesn't matter.
거꾸로 됐어요
아뇨, 됐어요
It's not like I don't have
a sense of humor.
나도 유머감각은
있는 사람일세
나도 가끔은
음담패설도 즐긴다네
Hell, I even enjoy a
naughty limerick every now and then.
때와 장소를 가려야지
There's a time and a place.
혹 아는 얘기 있나?
Unless you have a limerick right now.
없어? 알았네
나중에 팩스로 보내던가
No? Okay.
Well, you've got my fax number.
나 대신 뒤집어쓰다니
정말 고마워
I can't believe you did that.
That was sweet.
-Don't worry about it.
-You could've lost your job.
- 별거 아닌데요
- 짤릴 뻔 했는데도?
이런 귀여운 엉덩이로
일 찾는 건 식은 죽 먹기죠
Are you kidding me? With this
cute butt, I'd find work.
Thank you, you're great.
고마워, 정말이야
-You know what?
-What?
- 사실은요
- 뭔데?
I feel great.
나 기분 좋아요
In fact...
그래서...
What?
왜요?
It's just.. It took me so long
to get that desk organized.
그 책상 정리하느라
무지 애 먹었거든요
I'm sorry.
미안해요
There it is.
나왔다
What is going on?
무슨 일이죠?
We're waiting for the candy.
Bring out the candy!
사탕 기다리고 있어요
사탕 주세요!
Yeah, lady, give us candy.
그래요, 아줌마
사탕 내놔요!
Joey!
조이!
-What's up, buddy?
-What are you doing?
- 왜?
- 뭐하는 거야?
Waiting to get candy.
사탕 기다리잖아
Get in here.
냉큼 들어와
Hey, and you cannot smoke in here.
여긴 금연이에요
Merry Christmas.
메리 크리스마스
The candy is coming! I need
another 15 minutes for it to cool.
사탕 다 됐는데 식으려면
15분 정도 걸려요
All right, everybody, just be quiet.
Be quiet! Be quiet! Pipe down!
다들 조용히 해요
조용히! 조용히!
What is the matter with you people?
도대체 왜들 이래요?
This woman was trying to do a nice
thing for you.
이 사람은 좋은 일 하려는 건데
여러분과 친해지려고
사탕을 만들기 시작했는데
She was making candy
so she could get to know all of you...
이 친구 이름 아는 사람
아무도 없잖아요
and I'll bet that not one of you
can tell me her name.
그렇죠?
Am I right?
사탕 아줌마?
Candy Lady?
'사탕 아줌마'? 아뇨
No, not "Candy Lady."
알면 사탕 줄 건가요?
If we know it, can we have candy?
좋아요, 이렇게 해요
All right, you know what?
됐어요, 다 끝났어요
Forget it, you've ruined it.
다들 집에 돌아가요
Go home. You've ruined it.
안 돼요
댁들이 다 망쳤어요!
That's all wrong! You guys
ruined everything. You ruined it!
- 고마워
- 무슨 소릴
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
담배 피웠어?
Did you smoke?
아니, 골초 아줌마가
연기를 내 입에 불었거든
No, smokes-a-lot lady blew smoke
directly into my mouth.
괜찮아?
Are you okay?
괜찮아
조금 무섭긴 했지만
Fine, but it was
really scary for a while.
누가 문에
협박메모를 붙여놨어!
Someone slipped a threatening
note under the door!
미안해, 내가 붙였어
군중심리 때문에
Oh, yeah. Sorry about that.
Mob mentality or whatever.
와, 내가 해 냈어
내가 자전걸 탔어!
I can't believe it. I did it.
I rode a bike!
절대 못 탈 줄 알았는데
고마워
I never thought I'd be able
to do that. Thank you.
내가 아니라
너 자신한테 감사해
Oh, hey, don't thank me.
Thank yourself.
두려움에 맞서 극복한 건
바로 너니까
You're the one who faced your fears
and ultimately overcame them.
썰렁하다, 로스
청소년 드라마도 아니고
Don't be so corny, Ross.
It's not an After School Special.